In how to use psychological tests
And how to create a fair recruitment process with the help of the tests.
After the training you have quite a few choices of workplaces that you can apply for.
It depends a little on what you feel you have become interested in.
For example, you can work in primary care, at a health center.
Where you might be the first contact with someone who has started to feel bad,
Or that has a certain problem that they want to get help with.
Then you can also work at a school for example.
Where you work more preventively with staff and students to create a better school environment.
- Then you can also work with recruitment processes,
to develop recruitment processes.